It is time for the flag-lowering ceremony.
حان وقت مراسم إنزال العلم.
Please face the flag with respect.
يرجى مواجهة العلم باحترام.
I bet you're wondering,
أراهن أنك تتساءل،
"What is this, some kind of prank?"
"ما هذا، هل هو نوع من المقالب؟"
This is what they called the flag-lowering ceremony.
هذا ما أطلقوا عليه اسم مراسم إنزال العلم.
Our dear Mr. President's own invention.
اختراع رئيسنا العزيز.
And that wasn't all.
ولم يكن ذلك كل شيء.
After midnight, you couldn't even be out on the streets.
بعد منتصف الليل، لا يمكنك حتى التواجد في الشوارع.
It was to crack down on decadent trends
كان الهدف هو القضاء على النزعات الانحلالية
that threatened public morals and order or whatever.
ذلك الذي يهدد الأخلاق العامة والنظام أو ما شابه.
SEX INDUSTRY
صناعة الجنس
Men were banned from growing sideburns over their ears,
مُنع الرجال من إطالة سوالفهم فوق آذانهم.
and women in miniskirts were punished for indecent exposure.
وكانت النساء اللواتي يرتدين التنانير القصيرة يُعاقبن على التعري غير اللائق.
Curfews.
حظر التجول.
No assemblies.
ممنوع التجمعات.
No protests.
لا احتجاجات.
No long hair and no miniskirts, either.
ممنوع الشعر الطويل وممنوع التنانير القصيرة أيضاً.
TO RESTORE SOCIAL DISCIPLINE
لاستعادة الانضباط الاجتماعي
IMMEDIATE DEPORTATION
الترحيل الفوري
People were monitored, raided, beaten, and killed.
كان الناس يخضعون للمراقبة والمداهمة والضرب والقتل.
KIM DAEJUNG RETURNED HOME
عاد كيم داي جونغ إلى الوطن
If they could go after heavyweight opposition politicians,
لو استطاعوا ملاحقة سياسيين معارضين بارزين،
imagine what they did to ordinary people.
تخيل ما فعلوه بالناس العاديين.
We were basically treated like cattle, like pigs.
لقد عوملنا بشكل أساسي كالمواشي، كالخنازير.
But the very ones leading the crackdowns?
لكن ماذا عن أولئك الذين يقودون حملات القمع؟
They lived above every ban.
لقد عاشوا فوق كل حظر.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I'm talking about the country's very first intelligence agency, the KCIA.
أنا أتحدث عن أول وكالة استخبارات في البلاد ، وهي وكالة الاستخبارات المركزية الكورية (KCIA).
GLOBAL SPY RING EXPOSED
كشف النقاب عن شبكة تجسس عالمية
With immense power that even eclipsed the Constitution,
بقوة هائلة فاقت حتى الدستور،
the KCIA propped up our dear Mr. President's long reign.
لقد دعمت وكالة المخابرات المركزية الكورية (KCIA) فترة حكم رئيسنا العزيز الطويلة.
Just the name of it was enough to strike fear.
كان مجرد ذكر اسمه كافياً لإثارة الخوف.
REVOLUTIONARY UNIFICATION PARTY SPY CASE
قضية تجسس تابعة لحزب التوحيد الثوري
So many innocent people were dragged off, and lost their lives.
تم اقتياد الكثير من الأبرياء، وفقدوا حياتهم.
Honestly though,
بصراحة،
I never thought I'd be one of them.
لم أتخيل يوماً أن أكون واحداً منهم.
This was the age of prohibition, and my name says it all.
كان هذا عصر الحظر، واسمي يغني عن كل شيء.
I'm Geumji, as in prohibition. Bae Geumji.
أنا غيومجي، كما في كلمة "حظر". باي غيومجي.
Madam, bar girl, escort, hostess.
سيدتي، فتاة بار، مرافقة، مضيفة.
Call me whatever you want.
نادني بما شئت.
What matters is that I was
المهم أنني كنت
damn good at what I did.
أنا بارعٌ جداً فيما أفعله.
But still,
لكن مع ذلك،
it's not a crime worth dying for, right?
إنها ليست جريمة تستحق الموت من أجلها، أليس كذلك؟
GIMPO AIRPORT, KOREA
مطار جيمبو، كوريا
Passengers for boarding, please proceed to Gate Three
الركاب المستعدون للصعود إلى الطائرة، يرجى التوجه إلى البوابة رقم ثلاثة.
of the International Terminal after completing immigration.
من مبنى الركاب الدولي بعد إتمام إجراءات الهجرة.
Seriously?
بجد؟
No one's here?
لا أحد هنا؟
Wow.
رائع.
This is unbelievable.
هذا لا يُصدق.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
THE AGE OF PROHIBITION
عصر الحظر
All right, all right.
حسناً، حسناً.
When we get there, it won't just be Mr. Cheon waiting.
عندما نصل إلى هناك، لن يكون السيد تشون وحده في الانتظار.
Bae Geumji will be there too.
ستكون باي غيومجي هناك أيضاً.
Yes, sir. Understood.
نعم سيدي. مفهوم.
They were nice enough to send her off to the States.
لقد كانوا لطفاء بما يكفي لإرسالها إلى الولايات المتحدة.
She should've stayed put and raised her kid quietly.
كان عليها أن تبقى في مكانها وتربي طفلها بهدوء.
What good did she think would come of this?
ما الفائدة التي كانت تعتقد أنها ستجنيها من هذا؟
I hear she's a woman with no fear.
سمعت أنها امرأة لا تعرف الخوف.
Yeah, I'll give her that.
نعم، سأعترف لها بذلك.
Using her own damn kid like that.
تستغل طفلها اللعين بهذه الطريقة.
Do you know, sir?
هل تعلم يا سيدي؟
Who the father is.
من هو الأب؟
There are a lot of rumors.
هناك الكثير من الشائعات.
Hey.
يا.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Just keep your eyes on the road.
أبقِ عينيك على الطريق.
Unless you've got a death wish.
إلا إذا كنت تتمنى الموت.
Have you met Mr. Cheon before?
هل سبق لك أن قابلت السيد تشون؟
No, this is my first time in person.
لا، هذه أول مرة لي شخصياً.
Born into the elite and
وُلِدَ في صفوف النخبة و
top of his class at the Military Academy.
كان الأول على دفعته في الأكاديمية العسكرية.
He caught the President's eye during the revolution,
لفت انتباه الرئيس خلال الثورة،
and now, he throws around more weight than ever.
والآن، أصبح يمتلك قوة أكبر من أي وقت مضى.
No.
لا.
Cheon Seokjung…
تشون سيوكجونغ…
…Chief of the Presidential Security Service.
...رئيس جهاز الأمن الرئاسي .
Top of his class at the Military Academy, adored by the President.
كان الأول على دفعته في الأكاديمية العسكرية، وكان محبوباً من قبل الرئيس.
The President's power was practically Cheon Seokjung's to wield,
كانت سلطة الرئيس عملياً حكراً على تشون سيوكجونغ،
and the KCIA was his loyal private army.
وكانت وكالة المخابرات المركزية الكورية بمثابة جيشه الخاص المخلص.
I mean, look.
أعني، انظر.
I can't live in hiding forever anyway.
لا يمكنني العيش مختبئاً إلى الأبد على أي حال.
It's not like I'm not a criminal.
الأمر ليس كما لو أنني لست مجرماً.
I've got to sort things out somehow,
يجب أن أجد حلاً للأمور بطريقة ما.
and raise my boy Seongguk to not come up short next to anyone.
وأربي ابني سونغكوك لكي لا يكون أقل شأناً من أي شخص آخر.
You really think his father's going to sit back and watch?
هل تعتقد حقاً أن والده سيجلس مكتوف الأيدي ويشاهد؟
What kind of father can't stand to see
أي نوع من الآباء لا يستطيع تحمل رؤية
his own son succeed?
هل سينجح ابنه؟
You know better than anyone he's not a man to be trifled with.
أنت تعرف أكثر من أي شخص آخر أنه ليس رجلاً يُستهان به.
And I'm not a woman to be trifled with either.
وأنا لست امرأة يُستهان بها أيضاً.
Come on.
تعال.
It's not like I'm asking to be his wife.
الأمر ليس وكأنني أطلب أن أكون زوجته.
Hello, Mr. Cheon.
مرحباً، سيد تشون.
How have you been, sir?
كيف حالك يا سيدي؟
It's been a while, Mr. Hwang.
لقد مر وقت طويل يا سيد هوانغ.
Why have you been so busy?
لماذا كنت مشغولاً للغاية؟
Oh, no. Not at all.
لا، أبداً.
Just give me a call, and I'll come running anytime, sir.
اتصل بي فقط، وسأحضر إليك في أي وقت يا سيدي.
Ah… You wear a toupee, huh?
آه... أنت ترتدي شعرًا مستعارًا، أليس كذلك؟
- Let's take a walk. - Yes, sir.
- لنتمشى قليلاً. - حاضر سيدي.
That's when Baek Kitae saw with his own eyes…
عندها رأى بايك كيتاي بأم عينيه...
…what real, living power looked like.
...كيف تبدو القوة الحقيقية والنابضة بالحياة.
Ah, I got it.
آه، فهمت.
And then he decided
ثم قرر
to live a life like that man's,
أن تعيش حياة مثل حياة ذلك الرجل،
with wealth and power great enough
بثروة وسلطة عظيمتين بما يكفي
to bring the whole world to its knees.
لإخضاع العالم بأسره.
Hello, darling.
مرحباً يا عزيزتي.
I'm going to the restroom.
سأذهب إلى دورة المياه.
Care to join me?
هل ترغب بالانضمام إلي؟
And that's how we met.
وهكذا التقينا.
In the most romantic setting, as you can see,
في أجواء رومانسية للغاية، كما ترون،
in the company of those government idiots.
بصحبة هؤلاء الحمقى الحكوميين.
There's no need to worry about wiretaps here, sir.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن التنصت هنا يا سيدي.
It's so loud in here.
الضوضاء هنا عالية جداً.
Loud and perfect for a secret investigation HQ.
صاخب ومثالي لمقر تحقيق سري.
All right, let's eat.
حسناً، لنأكل.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Let me say this again, just in case.
دعوني أكرر هذا مرة أخرى، تحسباً لأي طارئ.
No one else can know about this place but us.
لا أحد غيرنا يعرف عن هذا المكان.
- Okay? - Yes, sir.
- حسناً؟ - نعم سيدي.
How's the search for Kang Daeil going?
كيف تسير عملية البحث عن كانغ داييل؟
Any progress?
هل من جديد؟
Yes, we're tracing him through his crew.
نعم، نحن نتعقبه من خلال طاقمه.
We should be able to pin him down soon.
ينبغي أن نتمكن من القبض عليه قريباً.
We have to find him.
علينا أن نجده.
Yes, sir. Understood.
نعم سيدي. مفهوم.
Apparently, Jo Manjae had his hands in every racket and made a fortune.
على ما يبدو، كان جو مانجاي متورطاً في كل أنواع الصفقات المشبوهة وجمع ثروة طائلة.
Smuggling, for starters,
التهريب، على سبيل المثال،
siphoning US army supplies, real estate speculation…
تهريب إمدادات الجيش الأمريكي، والمضاربة العقارية...
Even the toilet paper in government offices
حتى ورق التواليت في المكاتب الحكومية
has to pass through his hands.
يجب أن يمر عبر يديه.
He ate all that up by himself?
هل أكل كل ذلك بمفرده؟
Mm-mmm… He couldn't have.
ممم... لا يمكن أن يكون قد فعل ذلك.
I mean, look. We can't even have a meal without sharing.
يعني، انظر. لا نستطيع حتى تناول وجبة دون مشاركة.
You think he can hog the whole thing? How?
أتظن أنه يستطيع أن يستحوذ على كل شيء؟ كيف؟
He's got backing.
لديه دعم.
Mr. Jang.
السيد جانغ.
You think that's the KCIA, right?
أتظن أن هذا مقر وكالة الاستخبارات المركزية الكورية الجنوبية، أليس كذلك؟
The KCIA doing business with gangsters? That's nothing new.
هل تتعامل وكالة المخابرات المركزية الكورية مع العصابات؟ هذا ليس بالأمر الجديد.
I'm not even surprised.
أنا لست متفاجئاً على الإطلاق.
But why do you think they took Jo Manjae?
لكن لماذا تعتقد أنهم أخذوا جو مانجاي؟
I bet he pulled something shady.
أراهن أنه فعل شيئاً مريباً.
That must be why they hauled him in.
لا بد أن هذا هو سبب اعتقاله.
They chopped off the tail. Cut him off like this.
لقد قطعوا ذيله. قطعوه هكذا.
What? You think they killed him?
ماذا؟ أتظن أنهم قتلوه؟
Jo Manjae paid up massive sums to the KCIA.
دفع جو مانجاي مبالغ طائلة لوكالة المخابرات المركزية الكورية.
And that money went straight into Director Hwang's safe.
وذهبت تلك الأموال مباشرة إلى خزنة المدير هوانغ.
Some of it probably went further up the chain too.
وربما وصل بعضها إلى مستويات أعلى في التسلسل الهرمي أيضاً.
You mean there's someone above Hwang?
هل تقصد أن هناك شخصًا أعلى من هوانغ؟
-That's right. -And who could it be?
- هذا صحيح. - ومن عساه يكون؟
Well, I don't know that yet.
حسنًا، لا أعرف ذلك بعد.
But the election's right around the corner,
لكن الانتخابات باتت وشيكة.
and plenty of places need funding.
وهناك العديد من الأماكن التي تحتاج إلى تمويل.
I'm sure they'll restart his operations by rounding up the rest of his gang.
أنا متأكد من أنهم سيعيدون إطلاق عملياته من خلال القبض على بقية أفراد عصابته.
To do that, they must've kept either Jo Manjae or Kang Daeil alive.
وللقيام بذلك، لا بد أنهم أبقوا إما جو مانجاي أو كانغ دايل على قيد الحياة.
And you think it's Kang Daeil, right?
وتظن أنه كانغ دايل، أليس كذلك؟
We've got a shot only if Kang Daeil's alive.
لن تتاح لنا فرصة إلا إذا كان كانغ دايل على قيد الحياة.
My legs…
ساقاي…
I haven't seen you around before.
لم أرك من قبل.
I work under Director Hwang.
أعمل تحت إشراف المدير هوانغ.
But there's no future
لكن لا يوجد مستقبل
working under Hwang.
العمل تحت إشراف هوانغ.
Maybe under Cheon, that would be different.
ربما في عهد تشون، سيكون الوضع مختلفاً.
If you're interested,
إذا كنت مهتماً،
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Let's meet somewhere quiet later.
لنلتقي في مكان هادئ لاحقاً.
Just the two of us.
نحن الاثنان فقط.
- Huh? - I had him under me for a bit
- هاه؟ - لقد كان تحتي لبعض الوقت
in the army.
في الجيش.
He's pretty useful.
إنه مفيد للغاية.
His eyes are practically dripping with ambition.
عيناه تكادان تفيضان طموحاً.
Maybe it's from growing up with nothing.
ربما يعود ذلك إلى نشأتي في بيئة خالية من كل شيء.
- But he knows his place. - I'm getting tipsy. Give me one.
- لكنه يعرف حدوده. - بدأت أشعر بالدوار. أعطني واحدة.
They make quite the pair.
إنهما يشكلان ثنائياً رائعاً.
Not a bad pick.
ليس اختياراً سيئاً.
Thank you, sir.
شكراً لك سيدي.
Geumji. Bae Geumji…
جومجي. باي جومجي…
I can't get a read on how that woman's going to play this.
لا أستطيع أن أتوقع كيف ستتصرف تلك المرأة في هذا الموقف.
You want me to kill her?
هل تريدني أن أقتلها؟
I'm sorry, sir.
أنا آسف يا سيدي.
Don't do anything stupid.
لا تفعل أي شيء أحمق.
Just have him stick close to her for now.
دعه يبقى قريباً منها في الوقت الحالي.
Keep an eye on her so she can't pull anything.
راقبها جيداً حتى لا تتمكن من فعل أي شيء.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
That woman's got a notebook.
تلك المرأة تحمل دفتر ملاحظات.
A list of all the men she's slept with.
قائمة بجميع الرجال الذين نامت معهم.
Which means the kid's father has to be in there.
وهذا يعني أن والد الطفل يجب أن يكون موجوداً هناك.
Now, what's the real issue? Who the father is?
والآن، ما هي المشكلة الحقيقية؟ من هو الأب؟
That's not the real issue.
ليست هذه هي المشكلة الحقيقية.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
What matters isn't who the father is.
ليس المهم من هو الأب.
It's that
هذا هو
all those men whose names are in that notebook are losing sleep,
جميع الرجال الذين وردت أسماؤهم في تلك المفكرة يعانون من الأرق،
wondering if the boy is theirs.
يتساءلون عما إذا كان الصبي ابنهم.
That's the real problem.
هذه هي المشكلة الحقيقية.
Can we trust that information?
هل يمكننا الوثوق بتلك المعلومات؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
The guy who gave it to me? His name's in that notebook too.
الشخص الذي أعطاني إياه؟ اسمه موجود في تلك المفكرة أيضاً.
You'd better keep your head straight.
من الأفضل أن تحافظ على هدوئك.
She's the kind men fall for at first sight.
إنها من النوع الذي يقع الرجال في حبه من النظرة الأولى.
You don't have to worry about me, sir.
لا داعي للقلق عليّ يا سيدي.
Ashtray.
منفضة سجائر.
Be careful, all right?
انتبه، حسناً؟
You wouldn't want your name ending up in that notebook too.
لن ترغب بالتأكيد في أن ينتهي اسمك في ذلك الدفتر أيضاً.
I swear,
أقسم،
I don't get why everyone's dying to sink their teeth into me.
لا أفهم لماذا يتوق الجميع إلى التهامني.
Did Director Hwang ask you to get the notebook?
هل طلب منك المخرج هوانغ إحضار دفتر الملاحظات؟
What notebook?
أي دفتر ملاحظات؟
You must be curious,
لا بد أنك فضولي،
being the only one left in the dark.
كونه الوحيد الذي بقي في الظلام.
I'm not interested.
أنا لست مهتم
Really?
حقًا؟
Because I could tell you right now
لأنني أستطيع أن أخبرك الآن
who the father really is.
من هو الأب الحقيقي.
But you're not interested, right?
لكنك لست مهتماً، أليس كذلك؟
Are you messing with me?
هل تمزح معي؟
Oh, no.
أوه، لا.
You thought I was actually going to tell you?
هل ظننت أنني سأخبرك فعلاً؟
You're adorable.
أنتِ رائعة الجمال.
Anyway, I'm never going back to the States,
على أي حال، لن أعود إلى الولايات المتحدة أبداً.
so tell them to quit dreaming.
لذا قل لهم أن يكفوا عن الأحلام.
I'm staying right here.
سأبقى هنا.
Maybe even date a handsome guy like you.
ربما حتى تواعدي رجلاً وسيماً مثلك.
Aren't you sick of men by now?
ألم تملّي من الرجال الآن؟
Depends on who the man is.
الأمر يعتمد على هوية الرجل.
Since we're here, why don't we be straight with each other?
بما أننا هنا، فلماذا لا نكون صريحين مع بعضنا البعض؟
If you don't feel like talking about dating, we can talk business.
إذا لم ترغب في الحديث عن المواعدة، فيمكننا التحدث عن العمل.
Business?
عمل؟
I told you the other day, didn't I?
ألم أقل لك ذلك في اليوم الآخر؟
I could help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
Help me with what? And how exactly?
ماذا تريد أن تساعدني؟ وكيف تحديداً؟
Hmm.
همم.
Look who's finally showing some interest.
انظروا من أبدى اهتماماً أخيراً.
Being the President's right-hand man or whatever…
أن تكون الرجل الأيمن للرئيس أو ما شابه ذلك...
Who cares about that crap?
من يهتم بهذا الهراء؟
What matters is
المهم هو
how you got there.
كيف وصلت إلى هناك؟
You know well
أنت تعرف جيداً
how Hwang managed to get as far as he did,
كيف تمكن هوانغ من الوصول إلى هذا الحد؟
don't you?
أنت , لا؟
Now, just think how much more Cheon must've passed up above him.
والآن، فكر فقط في مقدار الفرص الإضافية التي فاتت تشون عليه.
An endless stream of cash.
تدفق نقدي لا ينقطع.
That's the real source of their power.
هذا هو المصدر الحقيقي لقوتهم.
So…
لذا…
If you had your hands on that stream,
لو كنت تملك القدرة على الوصول إلى ذلك البث،
who's to say
من يستطيع الجزم؟
you couldn't get to Cheon's level, not just Hwang's?
ألم تستطع الوصول إلى مستوى تشون، وليس فقط مستوى هوانغ؟
Am I right?
هل أنا على صواب؟
Mr. Baek.
السيد بايك.
Tell me what you want.
أخبرني ماذا تريد.
I'll help you.
سأساعدك.
I heard you've got ties to the Japanese yakuza.
سمعت أن لديك علاقات مع الياكوزا اليابانية.
Chairman Ikeda.
الرئيس إيكيدا.
Have you ever met him?
هل سبق لك أن قابلته؟
Boss!
رئيس!
No.
لا.
But I did catch a glimpse of his daughter once.
لكنني لمحت ابنته مرة واحدة.
Ikeda Yuji.
إيكيدا يوجي.
Real name, Choi Yuji.
الاسم الحقيقي: تشوي يوجي.
Yes, Choi Yuji.
نعم، تشوي يوجي.
How did you know she's Korean?
كيف عرفت أنها كورية؟
I've met her myself once.
لقد قابلتها بنفسي مرة واحدة.
If only she weren't of Korean descent,
لو لم تكن من أصل كوري،
she might have even had a shot at being his successor.
بل ربما كانت لديها فرصة لتكون خليفته.
She's a Zainichi, but he still took her in as his foster daughter.
هي من الزاينيتشي، لكنه مع ذلك تبناها كابنة بالتبني.
I don't know how she won his favor,
لا أعرف كيف نالت إعجابه،
but he clearly treasures her.
لكن من الواضح أنه يكن لها تقديراً كبيراً.
Anyway, I'm certain she's one of the real powers in the Ikeda clan.
على أي حال، أنا متأكد من أنها واحدة من القوى الحقيقية في عشيرة إيكيدا.
How on earth do you know all this?
كيف عرفت كل هذا؟
So, what about Choi Yuji?
إذن، ماذا عن تشوي يوجي؟
I think… …I need to see her again.
أعتقد... ...أنني بحاجة لرؤيتها مرة أخرى.
Hmm…
همم…
Okay.
تمام.
Call me, Mr. Baek.
نادني السيد بايك.
Guys, this is Lee Sunyeong.
يا جماعة، هذا لي سون يونغ.
She's a new member of Rose Club.
إنها عضوة جديدة في نادي روز.
Say hello.
قل مرحباً.
Hi, nice to meet you all.
مرحباً، تشرفت بلقائكم جميعاً.
I'm Lee Sunyeong.
أنا لي سون يونغ.
I'm not very good with my hands though.
لكنني لستُ بارعاً جداً في استخدام يديّ.
Anyway, I'm excited to be here.
على أي حال، أنا متحمس لوجودي هنا.
Come on, no one's good from the start.
هيا، لا أحد يكون جيداً منذ البداية.
- Welcome to the club. - Thanks.
- أهلاً بك في النادي. - شكراً.
Here, try knitting this first.
جربي حياكة هذا أولاً.
Hi, Soyeong.
مرحباً، سويونغ.
You got off work a bit late today.
لقد انتهيت من العمل متأخراً قليلاً اليوم.
Yeah.
نعم.
Oh, I see you guys have already started.
أوه، أرى أنكم قد بدأتم بالفعل.
Soyeong, did you get what I asked for last time?
سويونغ، هل حصلتِ على ما طلبته منكِ في المرة الماضية؟
Yeah, I brought the information sheet.
نعم، لقد أحضرت ورقة المعلومات.
It's a three-year term with an annual interest rate of 17.4%…
مدة القرض ثلاث سنوات بمعدل فائدة سنوي قدره 17.4%…
Oh, my gosh. Thank you so much, Soyeong.
يا إلهي. شكراً جزيلاً لكِ يا سويونغ.
Are you from Seoul?
هل أنت من سيول؟
Sorry?
آسف؟
You don't seem to have a Busan accent.
لا يبدو أن لديك لكنة بوسان.
That's because Soyeong grew up in Japan.
ذلك لأن سويونغ نشأت في اليابان.
Soyeong, say hello.
سويونغ، قولي مرحباً.
This is Lee Sunyeong. She's a new member of the club.
هذه لي سون يونغ. إنها عضوة جديدة في النادي.
Of course.
بالطبع.
No wonder you've got such great skin.
لا عجب أن بشرتك رائعة للغاية.
My goodness. How's your skin so smooth?
يا إلهي! كيف تحافظين على نعومة بشرتكِ؟
Oh, you're too kind.
أوه، أنت لطيف للغاية.
Well, I was just born with it.
حسناً، لقد ولدتُ بها فحسب.
You're so lucky.
أنت محظوظ جداً.
My uncle lives in Japan too. In Osaka.
عمي يعيش في اليابان أيضاً. في أوساكا.
No way! I lived in Osaka too!
مستحيل! لقد عشت في أوساكا أيضاً!
Oh, my goodness.
يا إلهي.
What are the chances?
ما هي الاحتمالات؟
-Wow, you work at a bank? -Oh, yeah.
- واو، أنت تعمل في بنك؟ - أوه، نعم.
What do you do for a living, Sunyeong?
ماذا تعملين لكسب عيشك يا سون يونغ؟
Well…
حسنًا…
My parents run… What do you call that again?
والداي يديران... ما اسم ذلك؟
They run a metal shop…
يديرون متجرًا للمعادن...
…so I help out with my older brothers.
لذلك أساعد إخوتي الأكبر سناً.
What about you, Soyeong?
وماذا عنكِ يا سويونغ؟
Do you have an older brother?
هل لديك أخ أكبر؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Well, I've never told you guys,
حسنًا، لم أخبركم بذلك من قبل يا رفاق،
but my brother could give Shin Seongil a run for his money.
لكن أخي يستطيع أن ينافس شين سيونجيل بقوة.
My brother looks like Alain Delon!
أخي يشبه آلان ديلون!
Really? We have so much in common!
حقاً؟ لدينا الكثير من القواسم المشتركة!
Wow, are they really that handsome?
يا إلهي، هل هم حقاً بهذه الوسامة؟
-You should bring him here sometime. -Oh, I can't do that. He's busy.
- يجب أن تحضره إلى هنا في وقت ما. - أوه، لا أستطيع فعل ذلك. إنه مشغول.
- Bring him. - I've got to see with my own eyes.
- أحضروه. - يجب أن أرى ذلك بنفسي.
- He must be really handsome. - You bet.
- لا بد أنه وسيم للغاية. - بالتأكيد.
The Vietnam War, huh?
حرب فيتنام، هاه؟
PERSONAL RECORD NAME: BAEK KITAE
اسم السجل الشخصي : بايك كيتاي
Yes.
نعم.
He was in the Special Warfare Command but got dishonorably discharged there.
كان يعمل في قيادة العمليات الخاصة، لكنه طُرد منها بطريقة غير مشرفة.
It seems like there was some kind of incident.
يبدو أن هناك حادثة ما قد وقعت.
Sir, I heard rumors you got the Order of Military Merit,
سيدي، سمعت شائعات بأنك حصلت على وسام الاستحقاق العسكري.
but that's not true, right?
لكن هذا ليس صحيحاً، أليس كذلك؟
Well…
حسنًا…
I mean, it was from the government,
أعني، لقد كان ذلك من الحكومة،
so I couldn't exactly refuse.
لذلك لم يكن بإمكاني الرفض تماماً.
Seriously?
بجد؟
There were three armed guerrillas.
كان هناك ثلاثة مقاتلين مسلحين.
Armed guerrillas?
مقاتلون مسلحون؟
You going to tell me you've been shot too?
هل ستخبرني أنك تعرضت لإطلاق نار أيضاً؟
-Here. -Huh?
-هنا. -هاه؟
- Here. - Wait.
- هنا. - انتظر.
Are you actually telling me this is from a gunshot?
هل تقول لي حقاً أن هذا ناتج عن طلق ناري؟
- It went in here and… - Yeah?
- دخل إلى هنا و... - أجل؟
- I'm not sure if you can see it. Here. - Whoa, what?
- لست متأكدًا مما إذا كان بإمكانك رؤيته. تفضل. - مهلاً، ماذا؟
Wait a second.
انتظر لحظة.
So it went in here and came out here?
إذن دخل من هنا وخرج من هنا؟
Wow, so it's true!
يا للعجب، هذا صحيح!
You're incredible, Mr. Jang.
أنت رائع يا سيد جانغ.
Well, they wouldn't have given me the medal if I weren't.
حسنًا، ما كانوا ليمنحوني الميدالية لو لم أكن كذلك.
Oh, my.
يا إلهي.
Oh, my…
يا إلهي...
Mr. Jang, you must work out all the time.
سيد جانغ، يجب عليك ممارسة الرياضة طوال الوقت.
Yeah, well, I just do some push-ups.
أجل، حسناً، أنا فقط أقوم ببعض تمارين الضغط.
Of course.
بالطبع.
No wonder you look so good in your suits.
لا عجب أنك تبدو أنيقاً جداً في بدلاتك.
How many do you do?
كم عدد الأشياء التي تقوم بها؟
A hundred? Yeah, about a hundred.
مئة؟ نعم، حوالي مئة.
So, how did it go?
إذن، كيف سارت الأمور؟
Did you meet her?
هل قابلتها؟
I'm so tired.
أنا متعب جدا.
It's true they grew up in Osaka, Japan.
صحيح أنهم نشأوا في أوساكا، اليابان.
- They're Zainichi? - Yes.
- هل هم من الزينيكيين؟ - نعم.
They came back to Korea after their parents passed.
عادوا إلى كوريا بعد وفاة والديهم.
Apparently, they had a tough time settling down here.
على ما يبدو، واجهوا صعوبة في الاستقرار هنا.
Then Baek Kitae must've had to play the parent.
إذن، لا بد أن بايك كيتاي قد اضطر إلى لعب دور الوالد.
He did every kind of job imaginable
لقد قام بكل أنواع الوظائف التي يمكن تخيلها
to support his younger siblings.
لدعم إخوته الصغار.
And being Zainichi, he went through a lot of discrimination.
وبصفته زينيتشي، فقد تعرض للكثير من التمييز.
So he became a career soldier?
هل أصبح جندياً محترفاً؟
There's actually another soldier in the family.
يوجد جندي آخر في العائلة.
Their younger brother, Baek Kihyun.
شقيقهم الأصغر، بايك كيهيون.
He graduated top of his class from the Military Academy.
تخرج من الأكاديمية العسكرية بتفوق .
Now, he's serving up front as a second lieutenant.
والآن، يخدم في الخطوط الأمامية برتبة ملازم ثانٍ.
The older brother's in the KCIA, and the younger one's from the Academy?
الأخ الأكبر يعمل في وكالة المخابرات المركزية، والأصغر من الأكاديمية؟
Well, talk about rising from nothing.
حسنًا، هذا مثال على النهوض من العدم.
But it sounded like something happened to the younger brother when he was a kid.
لكن يبدو أن شيئاً ما قد حدث للأخ الأصغر عندما كان طفلاً.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Well, Baek Soyeong didn't go into detail, but she seemed really worried about him.
حسناً، لم تدخل بايك سويونغ في التفاصيل، لكنها بدت قلقة عليه حقاً.
Okay.
تمام.
So, are you meeting her again?
إذن، هل ستلتقي بها مرة أخرى؟
Yes, we hit it off and decided to grab a meal together sometime.
نعم، لقد انسجمنا وقررنا تناول وجبة معًا في وقت ما.
Also, Kang Daeil?
إذن، كانغ دايل؟
He's alive.
إنه على قيد الحياة.
You've tracked him down?
هل عثرت عليه؟
Not exactly. But word is, he's putting the gang back together.
ليس تماماً. لكن يُقال إنه يُعيد تجميع العصابة.
He's even looking for a chemist.
بل إنه يبحث عن كيميائي.
See? I told you, Kang Daeil, that bastard, is alive.
أرأيت؟ لقد أخبرتك يا كانغ داييل، ذلك الوغد، أنه على قيد الحياة.
Your instincts are spot-on, sir.
حدسك صحيح تماماً يا سيدي.
I'm telling you,
أقول لك،
Kang Daeil is tied up with the KCIA.
كانغ دايل متورط مع وكالة المخابرات المركزية الكورية.
The KCIA can take down anyone in their sights.
بإمكان وكالة الاستخبارات المركزية الكورية (KCIA) القضاء على أي شخص يقع في مرمى نيرانها.
Mr. Jang, if you push too far and things go sideways--
سيد جانغ، إذا تجاوزت الحد وساءت الأمور...
I'll take the fall.
سأتحمل المسؤولية.
If anyone loses their job, it's going to be me.
إذا فقد أي شخص وظيفته، فسأكون أنا.
OSAKA, JAPAN
أوساكا، اليابان
You have guests from Korea.
لديكم ضيوف من كوريا.
Long time no see, Ms. Bae.
لم أركِ منذ مدة طويلة يا آنسة باي.
It's good to see you, Ms. Ikeda.
من دواعي سروري رؤيتك يا آنسة إيكيدا.
It's been a while, Mr. Matsuda.
لقد مر وقت طويل يا سيد ماتسودا.
Or should I call you Mr. Baek Kitae now?
أم هل يجب أن أناديك السيد بايك كيتاي الآن؟
I'm Baek Kitae.
أنا بخير.
It's good to see you.
سررت برؤيتك.
You've got a lovely little place here.
لديك مكان صغير وجميل هنا.
How's the chairman doing?
كيف حال الرئيس؟
I heard he hasn't been well.
سمعت أنه لم يكن على ما يرام.
Is your son doing well?
هل ابنك بخير؟
He's… just like his father.
إنه... يشبه والده تماماً.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
When are you going back to America?
متى ستعود إلى أمريكا؟
I'm not going back.
لن أعود.
I've got some things to do in Korea.
لدي بعض الأمور التي يجب أن أقوم بها في كوريا.
And I've met someone I like.
وقد قابلت شخصاً أعجبني.
You haven't eaten, right?
أنت لم تأكل، أليس كذلك؟
Gosh, I'm starving.
يا إلهي، أنا أتضور جوعاً.
I heard there's a famous sushi place nearby.
سمعت أن هناك مطعم سوشي شهير في مكان قريب.
I actually made a reservation there when I heard you were coming.
في الواقع، قمت بالحجز هناك عندما سمعت أنك قادم.
Darling, you like sushi, right? This is great.
عزيزتي، أنتِ تحبين السوشي، أليس كذلك؟ هذا رائع.
Mr. Baek, you should have a drink with me instead.
سيد بايك، كان من الأفضل أن تشرب معي بدلاً من ذلك.
I have something to discuss in private.
لديّ موضوع أريد مناقشته على انفراد.
My staff will escort you, Ms. Bae.
سيرافقك موظفاي يا آنسة باي.
You've done your part.
لقد قمت بدورك.
Now, it's Mr. Baek's turn to finish things.
والآن، حان دور السيد بايك لإنهاء الأمور.
I'm sure he didn't come all this way just to have some sushi with me.
أنا متأكدة أنه لم يأتِ إلى هنا فقط ليتناول بعض السوشي معي.
Am I right, Mr. Baek?
هل أنا على صواب يا سيد بايك؟
Does Ms. Bae know why we're meeting?
هل تعلم الآنسة باي سبب لقائنا؟
No.
لا.
She wouldn't have the faintest idea.
لم يكن لديها أدنى فكرة.
So you want to do business with me in Jo Manjae's place?
إذن، هل تريد أن تتعامل معي بدلاً من جو مانجاي؟
A senior KCIA agent himself?
هل هو عميل كبير في وكالة المخابرات المركزية الكورية؟
Is that a problem?
هل هذا يمثل مشكلة؟
Does Director Hwang know?
هل يعلم المخرج هوانغ؟
Does he need to?
هل هو بحاجة إلى ذلك؟
By the way… …how do you know him?
بالمناسبة... كيف تعرفه؟
I used to work with him.
كنت أعمل معه سابقاً.
On what?
على ماذا؟
Just some business.
مجرد بعض الأعمال.
"Chairman of the Korea-Japan Cultural Exchange Foundation."
"رئيس مجلس إدارة مؤسسة التبادل الثقافي بين كوريا واليابان ".
"Director of the Korea-Japan Development Council."
"مدير مجلس التنمية الكوري الياباني ".
Since when do yakuza do this kind of thing?
منذ متى والياكوزا يفعلون هذا النوع من الأشياء؟
We do anything that makes money,
نفعل أي شيء يدرّ علينا المال.
just like you.
مثلك تماماً.
Are you serious about doing this right?
هل أنت جاد في القيام بهذا الأمر بشكل صحيح؟
If we're not doing it right,
إذا لم نكن نفعل ذلك بشكل صحيح،
then I'm not doing it at all.
إذن لن أفعل ذلك على الإطلاق.
If you don't hold up your end again,
إذا لم تفِ بالتزاماتك مرة أخرى،
I'll make sure you pay for it, even for wasting my time.
سأحرص على أن تدفع ثمن ذلك، حتى لو كان ذلك مقابل إضاعة وقتي.
That sounds like a threat.
هذا يبدو كتهديد.
It is a threat.
إنه تهديد.
If you can't handle it, walk away.
إذا لم تستطع تحمل الأمر، فابتعد.
Let me ask you one thing.
دعني أسألك سؤالاً واحداً.
Did you want to see me?
هل كنت تريد رؤيتي؟
I wanted to see you.
كنت أرغب برؤيتك.
Mr. Baek!
السيد بايك!
Darling, were you okay without me?
حبيبتي، هل كنتِ بخير بدوني؟
Did you enjoy shopping, Ms. Bae?
هل استمتعتِ بالتسوق يا آنسة باي؟
Yeah, I picked up a few briefs for my dear Mr. Baek.
نعم، لقد اشتريت بعض الملفات الشخصية للسيد بايك العزيز.
HAPPY BUSAN CITIZENS' DAY
عيد مواطنين سعيد في بوسان
Hello, Director Hwang.
مرحباً، المخرج هوانغ.
Jang Geonyoung, Special Investigations, Busan Office.
جانغ جيونيونغ، قسم التحقيقات الخاصة، مكتب بوسان.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
I heard you've been working hard chasing after those junkies.
سمعت أنك تعمل بجد في ملاحقة هؤلاء المدمنين.
Me? Not at all.
أنا؟ أبداً.
You're the one who must have it rough, sir.
أنت من يعاني يا سيدي.
With all the big names in Busan in the palm of your hand,
مع وجود جميع الأسماء الكبيرة في بوسان بين يديك،
I can only imagine how much work that takes.
لا يسعني إلا أن أتخيل حجم العمل الذي يتطلبه ذلك.
I don't know what you've heard exactly.
لا أعرف ما سمعته بالضبط.
But narcotics cases?
لكن ماذا عن قضايا المخدرات؟
You just end up chasing the tail all night.
ينتهي بك الأمر بمطاردة الذيل طوال الليل.
-You've got your share of headaches. -That's why
- لديك نصيبك من الصداع. - لهذا السبب
I was hoping to ask you for some intel.
كنت آمل أن أطلب منك بعض المعلومات.
What kind of intel?
أي نوع من المعلومات الاستخباراتية؟
You know Jo Manjae well, right?
أنت تعرف جو مانجاي جيداً، أليس كذلك؟
The Manjae Gang boss.
زعيم عصابة مانجاي.
Well, I guess I know about as much as you do.
حسناً، أعتقد أنني أعرف بقدر ما تعرف أنت.
But I was told
لكن قيل لي
he disappeared. Isn't that right?
لقد اختفى. أليس كذلك؟
Yes, that's right.
نعم، هذا صحيح.
He did disappear, without a trace.
لقد اختفى بالفعل، دون أن يترك أثراً.
But just when I started investigating again,
ولكن عندما بدأتُ التحقيق مجدداً،
a witness pops up saying they'd seen him in the Philippines.
يظهر شاهد ويقول إنه رآه في الفلبين.
And the next thing I know, the higher-ups shut it all down.
وفجأة، قام المسؤولون الكبار بإغلاق كل شيء.
So what exactly is it
ما هو بالضبط؟
that you want to know?
هل تريد أن تعرف؟
Whether he's alive in the Philippines
هل هو على قيد الحياة في الفلبين؟
or rotting somewhere, that can wait.
أو أن تتعفن في مكان ما، فهذا يمكن أن ينتظر.
But who has taken over his operation
لكن من الذي تولى إدارة عملياته؟
and is running the drug trade here in Busan?
وهل يدير تجارة المخدرات هنا في بوسان؟
That's what I want to know.
هذا ما أريد معرفته.
That's news to me.
هذا جديد بالنسبة لي.
Someone's definitely taken it over.
من المؤكد أن أحدهم قد استولى عليه.
I'm sure of it.
أنا متأكد من ذلك.
Rounding up the leftover goons,
جمع البلطجية المتبقين،
and trying to bring in a new cook.
ومحاولة جلب طاهٍ جديد.
Ah…
آه...
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I don't see your guy here. Baek Kitae?
لا أرى الشخص الذي تقصده هنا. بايك كيتاي؟
He's usually with you.
هو عادةً ما يكون معك.
I guess the KCIA must be swamped these days.
أظن أن مكتب التحقيقات الجنائية في كوالالمبور يعاني من ضغط هائل هذه الأيام.
You're good at peeling these.
أنت بارع في تقشير هذه.
I can never get it right.
لا أستطيع أن أتقنها أبداً.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
-Want me to peel one for you? -Would you?
- هل تريدني أن أقشر لك واحدة؟ - هل ستفعل؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Here.
هنا.
You grab the legs
تمسك بالساقين
and peel it off like this.
وانزعه هكذا.
There.
هناك.
-For you, sir. -Thanks.
- لك يا سيدي. - شكراً.
-Go ahead. -All right.
- تفضل. - حسناً.
Mr. Jang!
السيد جانغ!
How did it go?
كيف سارت الأمور؟
Seeing how he played dumb,
بعد أن رأينا كيف تظاهر بالغباء،
it's clear the KCIA took care of Jo Manjae.
من الواضح أن وكالة المخابرات المركزية الكورية اعتنت بجو مانجاي.
So, does that mean Director Hwang killed him off
هل يعني ذلك أن المخرج هوانغ قتله؟
and is pushing meth himself?
وهل يروج هو نفسه للميثامفيتامين؟
I don't think Director Hwang knows much about the drugs.
لا أعتقد أن المخرج هوانغ يعرف الكثير عن المخدرات.
Then who the hell is it?
إذن من يكون بحق الجحيم؟
When are you meeting Baek Soyeong?
متى ستلتقي ببايك سويونغ؟
Do you think…
هل تعتقد...
Baek Kitae is trying to push meth behind Hwang's back?
هل يحاول بايك كيتاي ترويج الميثامفيتامين سراً عن هوانغ؟
I threw it out there,
لقد طرحت الفكرة،
so let's wait and see
فلننتظر ونرى
if Baek Kitae is really running drugs.
إذا كان بايك كيتاي يتاجر بالمخدرات بالفعل.
Have you lost your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
A KCIA agent dealing meth?
عميلٌ في وكالة الاستخبارات المركزية يتاجر بالميثامفيتامين؟
What are you thinking? Huh?
بماذا تفكر؟ ها؟
Are you trying to get us all killed?
هل تحاول أن تتسبب في قتلنا جميعاً؟
I'm doing this so we can all survive.
أفعل هذا حتى نتمكن جميعاً من البقاء على قيد الحياة.
After Mom died,
بعد وفاة أمي،
how did the three of us make it to Busan?
كيف وصلنا نحن الثلاثة إلى بوسان؟
And what's our life been like?
وكيف كانت حياتنا؟
If we keep living like this, nothing will be different in 10, 20 years.
إذا استمرينا في العيش على هذا النحو، فلن يتغير شيء خلال 10 أو 20 سنة.
We'll never get out of this damn hillside slum.
لن نخرج أبداً من هذا الحي الفقير اللعين على سفح التل.
Soyeong.
سويونغ.
Don't you trust me?
ألا تثق بي؟
Say I bring in just one kilo. That costs 200,000 won.
لنفترض أنني أحضرت كيلوغراماً واحداً فقط. سيكلف ذلك 200 ألف وون.
Cook it and sell it, that's 5 million. Ship it to Japan, 15 million.
اطبخها وبعها، هذا يعني 5 ملايين. أرسلها إلى اليابان، 15 مليون.
Fif…
خمسة…
Fifteen million won?
خمسة عشر مليون وون؟
Plus, I'm not doing this alone.
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، أنا لا أفعل هذا بمفردي.
People above me…
الناس فوقي...
We're all in on it.
كلنا متفقون على ذلك.
Above you? The KCIA?
فوقك؟ وكالة الاستخبارات المركزية الكورية؟
How high up?
إلى أي ارتفاع؟
Way up.
في الأعلى.
Which means there's no risk of getting caught.
وهذا يعني أنه لا يوجد خطر من أن يتم القبض عليك.
No.
لا.
There will be addicts.
سيكون هناك مدمنون.
It'll wreck the country, right when they're trying to build a new era.
سيدمر ذلك البلاد، في الوقت الذي يحاولون فيه بناء عهد جديد.
Kitae, no, I'd feel too guilty.
كيتاي، لا، سأشعر بالذنب الشديد.
You don't have to worry about that.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن ذلك.
We'll make it here,
سنصل إلى هنا،
but we'll ship it all out to Japan.
لكننا سنشحنها كلها إلى اليابان.
Japan?
اليابان؟
Yeah. We'll be bringing in foreign currency,
نعم. سنستورد العملات الأجنبية.
and we'll be the ones driving exports.
وسنكون نحن من يقود الصادرات.
If the business goes well,
إذا سارت الأمور على ما يرام،
we'll be doing our part in building the new era.
سنقوم بدورنا في بناء العصر الجديد.
Our family won't be left behind.
لن نترك عائلتنا وراءنا.
We'll be at the forefront if we get with the times.
سنكون في الطليعة إذا واكبنا العصر.
That means we're serving the country.
هذا يعني أننا نخدم الوطن.
It's patriotic work.
إنه عمل وطني.
Patriotic?
وطني؟
Yes.
نعم.
Don't tell Kihyun. He doesn't need to know.
لا تخبر كيهيون. ليس من الضروري أن يعرف.
Okay.
تمام.
You just need to take care of the money
كل ما عليك فعله هو الاهتمام بالمال
and keep an eye on Kang Daeil, all right?
وراقبوا كانغ داييل، حسناً؟
Mmm.
ممم.
Yeah. Thank you, sir.
نعم. شكراً لك سيدي.
Our goal…
هدفنا...
is to make the best product
الهدف هو صنع أفضل منتج
and take over the Japanese market.
والاستحواذ على السوق اليابانية.
What about Korea?
وماذا عن كوريا؟
Focus on Japan for now.
لنركز على اليابان في الوقت الحالي.
Don't put anything out in Korea without my approval.
لا تنشر أي شيء في كوريا دون موافقتي.
Understood.
مفهوم.
What about the chemist?
وماذا عن الكيميائي؟
We've got someone with sharp eyes and skilled hands.
لدينا شخص يتمتع بنظر حاد ومهارة عالية.
He's made quite a name for himself in this business.
لقد صنع لنفسه اسماً لامعاً في هذا المجال.
It wasn't easy, but I managed to bring him in.
لم يكن الأمر سهلاً، لكنني تمكنت من إحضاره.
The best of the best, as pure as possible.
الأفضل على الإطلاق، بأقصى درجات النقاء.
That's how we win the Japanese over.
هكذا نكسب اليابانيين.
You know that, right?
أنت تعلم ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Understood, sir.
مفهوم يا سيدي.
And I'm bringing one more person on board.
وسأضم شخصًا آخر إلى الفريق.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
The place has a nice view.
يتمتع المكان بإطلالة جميلة.
Right. Yeah, very nice.
صحيح. نعم، جميل جداً.
Let's do this!
هيا بنا نفعلها!
Yeah, let's do this!
أجل، هيا بنا نفعلها!
All right, the pigs are here.
حسناً، الخنازير هنا.
Okay, let's go.
حسناً، لنذهب.
Come on, let's go.
هيا بنا، لنذهب.
Go on, get in there.
هيا، ادخل إلى هناك.
They stink bad, huh?
رائحتهم كريهة، أليس كذلك؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Here, this will help.
هذا سيساعدك.
I'm Kang Daeil.
أنا كانغ دايل.
I've heard a lot about you.
لقد سمعت الكثير عنك.
If it ever gets tough, just let me know.
إذا واجهتك أي صعوبات، فأخبرني بذلك.
Tough? No way.
صعب؟ مستحيل.
This is patriotic work after all.
هذا عمل وطني في نهاية المطاف.
Patriotic?
وطني؟
That's nice.
هذا جميل.
Man, smells real sweet.
يا رجل، رائحته حلوة جداً.
Make sure they have plenty to eat!
تأكد من حصولهم على ما يكفي من الطعام!
We've got the pigs here.
لدينا الخنازير هنا.
You want to get started?
هل تريد البدء؟
Mr. Kang.
السيد كانغ.
I have a question.
لدي سؤال.
Why did you bring pigs here?
لماذا أحضرت الخنازير إلى هنا؟
They cost money, don't they?
إنها تكلف مالاً، أليس كذلك؟
It stinks when you cook meth, you know.
رائحة كريهة عندما تقوم بطهي الميثامفيتامين، كما تعلم.
And?
و؟
You cover it with the smell of pig crap.
تغطيها برائحة روث الخنازير.
Ah…
آه...
Hey.
يا.
What?
ماذا؟
DIRECTOR GENERAL HWANG GUKPYEONG
المدير العام هوانغ غوكبيونغ
This month's take looks a little light.
يبدو أن نصيب هذا الشهر قليل بعض الشيء.
Kang Daeil's still trying to pull the gang back together, so…
لا يزال كانغ دايل يحاول لم شمل العصابة، لذا...
Fine. More importantly,
حسناً. والأهم من ذلك،
who did she meet in Osaka?
من قابلت في أوساكا؟
Bae Geumji.
باي غومجي.
No one in particular.
لا أحد على وجه الخصوص.
She just went shopping and sightseeing.
ذهبت للتسوق ومشاهدة المعالم السياحية.
Shopping, huh?
التسوق، أليس كذلك؟
And I'm losing my mind over here.
وأنا أفقد صوابي هنا.
Where's that tramp now?
أين ذلك المتشرد الآن؟
She's staying with her family to take care of her kid.
إنها تقيم مع عائلتها لرعاية طفلها.
Lee's keeping an eye on her now.
لي يراقبها الآن.
I'll be taking over again tomorrow.
سأتولى الأمر مجدداً غداً.
Right, I appreciate it.
حسناً، أنا أقدر ذلك.
Phone in every two hours.
اتصل بنا كل ساعتين.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
You can go.
يمكنك الذهاب.
Send Pyo in.
أرسل بيو.
Yes, sir. I will.
نعم سيدي، سأفعل.
Mr. Pyo, he'll see you now.
السيد بيو، سيقابلك الآن.
- Did you find out? - Yes, sir.
- هل توصلت إلى ذلك؟ - نعم سيدي.
Baek Kitae met with Ikeda Yuji in Osaka.
التقى بايك كيتاي مع إيكيدا يوجي في أوساكا.
Choi Yuji?
تشوي يوجي؟
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Baek Kitae…
بايك كيتاي…
met with Choi Yuji?
هل التقى بتشوي يوجي؟
That little bastard.
ذلك الوغد الصغير.
I told him to shut down the meth business…
طلبت منه أن يغلق تجارة الميثامفيتامين...
…and now he's going all in on it?
...والآن هو يغامر بكل شيء؟
It looks like he and Kang Daeil have taken over the whole Manjae Gang.
يبدو أنه هو وكانغ دايل قد سيطرا على عصابة مانجاي بأكملها.
I guess I've been raising a tiger all along, huh?
أظن أنني كنت أربي نمراً طوال الوقت، أليس كذلك؟
If word gets out the KCIA's pushing meth, it'll be a hell of a show, won't it?
إذا انتشر خبر ترويج وكالة المخابرات المركزية للميثامفيتامين، فسيكون ذلك عرضاً مذهلاً، أليس كذلك؟
Sir.
سيد.
But the thing is,
لكن الأمر هو،
I hear the profits are massive.
سمعت أن الأرباح هائلة.
- Really? - Yes, sir.
- حقاً؟ - نعم سيدي.
How much are we talking?
كم السعر الذي نتحدث عنه؟
I'll get back to you with exact numbers.
سأعود إليك بالأرقام الدقيقة.
What did you pray for?
بماذا دعوت؟
The country's well-being and world peace.
رفاهية البلاد والسلام العالمي.
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.
Don't you ever pray?
ألا تصلي أبداً؟
Does He ever answer your prayers?
هل يستجيب الله لدعائك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
If you really want it with all your heart, He does.
إذا كنت تريده حقاً من كل قلبك، فهو يريده.
Ms. Bae, what is it that you really want?
يا آنسة باي، ما الذي تريدينه حقاً؟
Does the notebook even exist?
هل يوجد دفتر الملاحظات أصلاً؟
What about you? What do you really want?
ماذا عنك؟ ماذا تريد حقاً؟
Money?
مال؟
Power?
قوة؟
Love?
حب؟
You want it all, don't you?
تريد كل شيء، أليس كذلك؟
So no one can ever look down on you.
لذلك لا يمكن لأحد أن ينظر إليك بازدراء.
So do I.
اذا يمكنني.
Same as you.
مثلك تماماً.
Fucking hell.
يا للهول!
Bow properly, damn it!
انحنِ بشكل صحيح، اللعنة!
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hey, where the hell are you?
أين أنت بحق الجحيم؟
Where's Bae Geumji?
أين باي غومجي؟
She's attending church service.
إنها تحضر القداس في الكنيسة.
That bitch wants to see the President today!
تلك الحقيرة تريد رؤية الرئيس اليوم!
He'll be inspecting Seoul National University in a bit,
سيقوم بتفتيش جامعة سيول الوطنية بعد قليل.
and that crazy bitch is planning to show up there!
وتلك المجنونة تخطط للظهور هناك!
Hey!
يا!
If you lose her, you and I are finished. You get that, right?
إذا خسرتها، فستنتهي علاقتنا. أنت تفهم ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
You get that or not, you little shit?
هل فهمت ذلك أم لا، أيها الوغد الصغير؟
Bae Geumji!
باي غومجي!
Na Yongcheol, Chief of Staff to the President.
نا يونغتشول، رئيس أركان الرئيس.
Cheon Seokjung's sole rival and his closest enemy.
المنافس الوحيد لتشون سيوكجونغ وأقرب أعدائه.
You think you can just pop out a kid and turn your life around?
أتظنين أن بإمكانكِ إنجاب طفل وتغيير حياتكِ رأساً على عقب؟
Well, I figured I'd give it a try.
حسناً، فكرت في أن أجرب ذلك.
See if it works.
جربها لترى إن كانت ستنجح.
There's only one kid.
لا يوجد سوى طفل واحد.
How many fathers does he have?
كم عدد الآباء الذين لديه؟
You looking to milk everyone dry?
هل تسعى لاستنزاف أموال الجميع؟
Hmm…
همم…
You and I
أنت وأنا
both know
كلاهما يعرف
who the father is.
من هو الأب؟
What matters isn't the truth.
ليس المهم هو الحقيقة.
What matters is
المهم هو
what people believe, Mr. Na.
ما يعتقده الناس، يا سيد نا.
Either way, they all believe what they want to believe.
في كلتا الحالتين، كل منهم يؤمن بما يريد أن يؤمن به.
And?
و؟
You're just going to let them believe it?
هل ستتركهم يصدقون ذلك فحسب؟
Why not? It doesn't hurt me.
لماذا لا؟ لن يضرني ذلك.
There's no reason for me to run around telling people the whole story, is there?
ليس هناك سبب يدفعني للتجول وإخبار الناس بالقصة كاملة، أليس كذلك؟
Well, if it bothers you that much,
حسناً، إذا كان الأمر يزعجك إلى هذا الحد،
why don't you go ahead and tell them yourself?
لماذا لا تذهب وتخبرهم بنفسك؟
So the country can go to hell, as long as you save your own skin?
إذن فليذهب البلد إلى الجحيم، طالما أنك تنقذ نفسك؟
All those men you're stirring up
كل هؤلاء الرجال الذين تثيرينهم
are those working hard to keep this country going.
هم أولئك الذين يعملون بجد للحفاظ على استمرار هذا البلد.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Which is why I'm asking for your help.
ولهذا السبب أطلب مساعدتكم.
I want to be able to care about the country too.
أريد أن أكون قادراً على الاهتمام بالبلاد أيضاً.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
you could really end up dead if you keep this up.
قد ينتهي بك الأمر ميتاً حقاً إذا استمريت على هذا المنوال.
Don't you know any of them could easily get rid of someone like you?
ألا تعلم أن أياً منهم يستطيع التخلص من شخص مثلك بسهولة؟
Doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
No matter what anyone says, I'm not leaving.
مهما قال أي شخص، لن أغادر.
So help me.
فليساعدني الله.
Come on. After everything…
هيا. بعد كل شيء...
I can ask you that much, can't I?
أستطيع أن أطلب منك هذا القدر، أليس كذلك؟
Hmm?
همم؟
Truth is,
والحقيقة هي،
I've been thinking of starting my own business.
كنت أفكر في بدء مشروع تجاري خاص بي.
I've always wanted to.
لطالما رغبت في ذلك.
A courtesan house, bigger than Cheonungak.
بيت للبغايا، أكبر من تشونونغاك.
How does that sound?
ما رأيك في ذلك؟
I've already got my eye on the building and the land.
لقد وضعت عيني بالفعل على المبنى والأرض.
Hmm…
همم…
And I think I'd like a villa too. Everyone else has one.
وأعتقد أنني أرغب في امتلاك فيلا أيضاً. فالجميع يمتلك واحدة.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Mr. Na.
السيد سو.
Don't take this lightly.
لا تستهن بهذا الأمر.
Because everything I said today?
لأن كل ما قلته اليوم؟
I meant every word.
كنت أعني كل كلمة قلتها.
You crazy bitch.
يا لكِ من امرأة مجنونة.
Are you threatening me right now?
هل تهددني الآن؟
So, you're saying…
إذن، أنت تقول...
She went to see
ذهبت لرؤية
Chief Na, not the President?
الزعيم نا، وليس الرئيس؟
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
That crazy bitch.
تلك العاهرة المجنونة.
She's digging her own grave, isn't she?
إنها تحفر قبرها بنفسها، أليس كذلك؟
What about Baek?
وماذا عن بايك؟
He's standing by in Seoul.
إنه ينتظر في سيول.
Goddamn idiot, falling for some tramp like that.
يا له من أحمق! كيف يقع في حب عاهرة كهذه؟
Still, the woman's a real piece of work.
ومع ذلك، فإن هذه المرأة شخصية غريبة الأطوار حقاً.
She just had to stir up the hornet's nest
كان عليها فقط أن تثير غضب الدبابير
and throw all the men upstairs into chaos.
وألقي بجميع الرجال في الطابق العلوي في حالة من الفوضى.
I can't tell if she's naïve or just plain stupid.
لا أستطيع أن أحدد ما إذا كانت ساذجة أم غبية بكل بساطة.
-Hey. -Yes, sir?
-مرحباً. -نعم سيدي؟
Have you ever been in love?
هل سبق لك أن أحببت؟
I'm not so sure.
لست متأكداً تماماً.
She's pulling all this shit just because she wants to be loved.
إنها تفعل كل هذا الهراء لمجرد أنها تريد أن تُحَب.
Fucking bitch.
يا لكِ من عاهرة لعينة.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
This was the night I last saw him.
كانت هذه الليلة التي رأيته فيها آخر مرة.
It was the first time he'd ever asked to meet,
كانت تلك المرة الأولى التي يطلب فيها اللقاء،
so I wondered what it was about.
لذا تساءلت عما يدور حوله الأمر.
Darling.
محبوب.
Are you mad at me?
هل أنت غاضب مني؟
Go back.
عُد.
Are you really going to do this?
هل ستفعل هذا حقاً؟
You're ruining the mood.
أنت تفسد الجو.
Those guys can't do anything to me.
هؤلاء الرجال لا يستطيعون فعل أي شيء لي.
I've got my notebook.
لدي دفتر ملاحظاتي.
Hand that over and get out of the country
أعطِ ذلك واخرج من البلاد
if you want to stay alive.
إذا كنت تريد البقاء على قيد الحياة.
If I hand that over…
إذا سلمت ذلك...
they'll kill me.
سيقتلونني.
And they'll kill you if you don't.
وسوف يقتلونك إن لم تفعل.
Why are you trying to scare me like this?
لماذا تحاول إخافتي هكذا؟
Enough games.
كفى ألعاباً.
Hand over the notebook, now.
سلم الدفتر الآن.
And if I don't?
وماذا لو لم أفعل؟
You might not make it through the night.
قد لا تتمكن من النجاة من هذه الليلة.
My God.
يا إلاهي.
How do you even make threats look so cool?
كيف تجعل التهديدات تبدو بهذه الروعة؟
Do you practice in front of a mirror or something?
هل تتدرب أمام المرآة أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Gosh, that hurt.
يا إلهي، لقد كان ذلك مؤلماً.
It never existed.
لم يكن موجوداً قط.
The notebook.
المفكرة.
I'm telling you the truth
أقول لك الحقيقة
because I think you figured that out a long time ago.
لأنني أعتقد أنك أدركت ذلك منذ زمن طويل.
Stay with me tonight.
ابقَ معي الليلة.
I don't want to be alone.
لا أريد أن أبقى وحيداً.
You said I might not make it through the night.
قلتَ إنني قد لا أستطيع الصمود طوال الليل.
If something happens to me,
إذا حدث لي مكروه،
you'll have to save me.
سيتعين عليك إنقاذي.
Why should I do that?
لماذا عليّ أن أفعل ذلك؟
You think I don't know?
أتظن أنني لا أعرف؟
About whatever deal you've got going with Choi Yuji.
بخصوص أي اتفاق لديك مع تشوي يوجي.
Did you think I wouldn't figure it out?
هل ظننت أنني لن أستطيع اكتشاف ذلك؟
You can't do this to me.
لا يمكنك فعل هذا بي.
You…
أنت…
Darling.
محبوب.
You like me, don't you?
أنت معجب بي، أليس كذلك؟
Mr. Baek.
السيد بايك.
Darling.
محبوب.
Hey, Seongguk's birthday is…
مرحبًا، عيد ميلاد سونغكوك هو...
Next Saturday.
السبت القادم.
How about we take him to Changgyeongwon?
ما رأيك أن نأخذه إلى تشانغيونغوون؟
And show him the elephants.
وأريه الأفيال.
Geumji, we should stop this now.
جيومجي، يجب أن نوقف هذا الآن.
Let's go back to the States with Seongguk, all right?
لنعد إلى الولايات المتحدة مع سونغكوك، حسناً؟
I'll do whatever it takes to raise him well.
سأفعل كل ما يلزم لتربيته تربية حسنة.
Aren't you angry?
ألا تشعر بالغضب؟
I am.
أنا أكون.
At this world.
في هذا العالم.
Hey. Get out of the car, punk.
هيا، انزل من السيارة أيها الوغد.
Who the hell are you?
من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
- Get out of the car. - Who the hell are you?
- انزل من السيارة. - من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
- Come on. - Let go! Let go of me!
هيا بنا! اتركني! اتركني!
- Walk straight, you bastard! - Who the hell are you?
- امشِ باستقامة أيها الوغد! - من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
- Hey, get him in. - Hey! Damn it.
- هيا، أدخله. - هيا! اللعنة.
- Get off me! - Get the hell in!
- ابتعد عني! - ادخل فوراً!
What's going on? You scared me.
ما الذي يحدث؟ لقد أرعبتني.
Can't you just let me go?
ألا يمكنك أن تدعني أذهب؟
I wanted to fall in love again.
أردت أن أقع في الحب مرة أخرى.
Translated by Yoonjung Song
ترجمة: يونجونغ سونغ